[Music]
um
firstly thank you very much to the
organizers we are humbled
and i feel really privileged to be part
of a team
uh that's been recognized for our work
around learning and development and
talent acquisition
um a credential right our
purpose is around innovating to help
everyone live well and
i my team has done extremely well in
bringing that narrative
into mind in everything that we have
curated in so far
as learning opportunities for our people
but more importantly also
being very clear about the proposition
we have to offer
not just our employees but also our
prospective employees
we are a purpose-led values-driven
organization
and this narrative has been i would say
at the heart
of our single-mindedness in providing
the right
experiences for our people our employee
value proposition is around creating
something new
and creating something new just doesn't
happen it does require
us to be very clear about what our
people need
to function in the future
what can we do to create the right
experiences for our people
but more importantly how do we attract
the right people the right talent
to be part of this journey to ensure
that we're just not
a great employer but we are a great
employer that is focused on delivering
value to our customers
so we we're really lucky we've got 28
nationalities
we have people from all sorts of
background a very strong local core
but a core that is very committed on
providing the right customer experiences
[Music]
uh no man's an island and my team and i
are very very privileged to be part of
this organization because
first and foremost we serve thousand
three hundred people
we serve people who come in every day to
add value
and that in itself is a privilege so a
big shout out to the people of
prudential
um our leaders okay
all of this is only possible if the
leaders believe
that people are truly our asset um
it's a cliched statement that many
people use but at pax at prudential
we live it and and our people have
continuously demonstrated
particularly through this pandemic as
well how adaptable how resilient and how
agile they are so
to our leaders for leading from the
front
uh last but not least my team
oh what a bunch of amazing human beings
who
are just up for any challenge
any time of the day so i feel very
privileged to leave